Oh, guys.
You're here first thing, oh, welcome back.
I mean, I was, you know,
your second charisma.
Yeah, I don't know what that was about, like.
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't know he was gonna put pictures though.
I don't want people to do that.
It's not so doxing.
And then I just don't know what people just,
when I end, I showed your picture
and then he said something really nasty and,
I just wanted to start over.
It was also, I think it would be better for,
I think,
I don't think I had my last title was very good. So let's go guys
So hey Maya, how are you good to see ya doing good. Yeah, he put up your picture and then he said that
Hi Jamie
Thank you guys welcome back you put you put up that you put up your picture on this profile, which is not supposed I
I'm like I'm telling people like please stop doing that because that's like a new thing people started doing
And it's like some people, yeah.
Yeah, it's a restart.
Yeah, so this might as good a restart sometimes
is because then it will just like
maybe go new on the algorithm, right?
I know Charisma, I know.
So I, you know, it's my, you know,
I understand because I have a lot of people
that are hard to wrangle.
I'll say it's like hard to like,
hey, it's like having like, you know,
a class full of like all ADHD kind of people if the it's gonna it's a little
patience to right thank you thank you Hannah but I'm gonna have to be tougher
on it because people keep doing it right yeah well yeah
Yeah, yesterday, but I mean a lot of people a lot of people have been doing that shit. Hey amber. Hey, Jamie's
No, but I do like to see what people will say sometimes like I or like I
Like I always like people are kind of a mystery and so when they like come up
Kind of like out of the right there randomly like he does like it's like what's he trying?
I want to see what he's trying to say, but
What is going on? Let's go in on what's going on nothing. I just restart I started a new stream of fresh midnight
It is now almost midnight
Hey, Hannah
How are you hey theme that is
But we're fine everything. Oh, what's going on Jamie? What do you mean? What's going on?
Because it's been like kind of weird around here lately
What's going on it's just
Price of fame. I know what's going on. Isn't that true? Like I see like
Yeah, yesterday it was like five people. I was like there's something like
That's why I was like it's a spiritual war instead of like some kind of like this coincidence of people
Because we're always drinking and hanging out and stuff. It's it's gotten it's getting like
Weird just getting people look are acting kind of weird. He's kicked out of everywhere. He only joined years in Jaycee's panel. Oh
Never thought yeah. Yeah, I never thought with I never thought with Jamie
And I've known Jamie for probably longer than most people and that I've known most people here in the chat
Like I've I've known her since I started my doing my before I doing I started doing my live streams
We're on discord. You know discord, I think
And she's been with me since the beginning
Never have a problem
Say for your side, how are you? Do you guys hear me or no? I don't think I put on my mic my microphone
Did you guys hear me? Okay. I was I'm my my mic wasn't on the right thing like the light show. I'll turn up to the light here
Okay
There you go
Good
Yeah, I could maybe my my mic wasn't on it first or it was on the iPad I guess yeah, this is the world bore else
I can also just pick it one color. I'll try to do that here. I think this one right there. It's pretty cool
Team who guys just team was six to solid fifty cents. What a what a cool thing
He's looking at her bar
At least you can rip the vape. Yeah, I'm gonna get some weed probably pretty soon
Maybe tomorrow. I'll see but I plan on ripping the ball
I
Like the vape but the vape seems to last how many get that vape maybe it's awesome. It was a week
Yeah, LD LD you're not supposed it's like even if you're fighting with people
To show put pictures up and stuff is kind of like
Hello, and it's not a lot of my show. Okay
Amber
Hey, there's Bunky Jamie's neck. What's up everybody? Yeah, that's pretty cool
Pretty cool
Facts
I mean that yeah, I know it's isn't it been a crazy weekend though. I think you know why you know why it's going so crazy right now I
Think isn't today isn't it the summer solstice today or yesterday? What is the summer solstice the 21st or 22nd?
But it's the summer solstice and so this is like what the summer solstice that you like the Sun is the highest in the sky
Yeah
So, it is a big celestial event, you know, every year, and so maybe that's one of the
reasons there's like, you know, and it is, you know, the summer, so it's gonna be the
hot sun.
I think the hot sun can provoke some kind of emotion, it was the 21st, so it was yesterday,
so that, I mean, it lines right up with, yeah, because that was yesterday, like, now it's
midnight, football one, so that line was perfect, it was, it was in summer solstice, guys, that's
why things were going kind of crazy.
Hi
Ghosty are you crashing out?
You're muted sir
crashing out
My Wi-Fi is crashing out. Oh
Are you doing okay? How's your night?
But you just said though the summer. Yeah, that's the day
Yeah, it was it was technically and now it's the 22nd, but yeah, well, yeah, I guess technically yeah, it's the next day now, but yeah
I was uh
It's the longest day of the year, I believe
Yeah, long as they have yet it was just it was crazy because it was also like there's so much
Uh, so much drama happening yesterday and all these
Biting with the whole pride. I'm not gonna bring it up with the whole but president thing. Oh my god. Yeah
A lot happening, dude. I mean I'm talking about just some on my even I'm not paying
I mean on my show, you know, like I had a band Alex at a band Alex
Joker again went off on me good times went off on me
Crystal went off on me, Bita went off on me, Mr. Goodtimes went off on me, Q went off on me, and then today it's like
some more stuff happening. Now listen here, here's what's going to make your night though. I'm not going to go off on you.
Well good. Don't crash out on me, Ghost. I can't have you do that. Hey, look at baby. Look at Dookie.
What kind of look? Can I ask you what kind of light is that?
A light? I don't know if you've shown me before. Oh, this one? My light? Yeah.
This is a, it's a, I got it on TV. Oh, that one, that one. Mine or his?
No, no, no you psyche the fucking light that's playing behind you. It's a roar. It's a roar borealis
I can like a little projector like a little or borealis
Was a little project. Yeah, it can make a different colors. It's an LED projector. Oh
Like that like that pretty cool. Six bucks 50 cents. I'm team you
Well, Bobby
Hi, that's a beautiful greyhound. Yeah, he's my he's my best boy right here
So my child that dog's nice, but let me tell you what them classes
They're working brother
dollar store I
Can see myself do them motherfuckers
Every time I buy like expensive sunglasses like they fucking go missing and what's the point? Yeah, like I always unless you like it
Because it's true that if you have like a vision issues, you know, like you have to buy like prescription sunglasses usually insurance covers it
But that's the only time I can leave an imagined buying experience. You know, I bought a dollar fucking
driving at night
We're the same
Yeah, I mean like, you know, do you know that expense like even like designer sunglasses
They're made at the same factory as like cheap sunglasses and you only like really you have to go buy at the store for like the really high quality
Like the ones that are like, you know, really really high quality good point that $400 designer glasses are no more
30 or you shop at Walmart. I'm sure sometimes but like even the great value shit
They do at the same fucking place. It's just they they do it on purpose. Like I just watched a documentary about it
Yeah
So what's going on this dude got a red all of a sudden he just after he cut out with his wife
I became all red red like that. I'm not gonna go put on a red sunglasses. Oh, oh my god. We got a warrant for a road road
Change let's go. I got some fat fucking felon and chat talking shit to me like
Well, I would just say he's a fat fucking felon I wouldn't worry about it. I
This is what she says quote. I just won't let some anorexic dog abusing child texting tar talk shit to me
I'm literally sleeping in my bed at home with my dog who I've had for multiple years. I work as a nurse
I've never been arrested and Amber you got popped for fucking met with your kid at home
Shut the fuck up bitch like
You got no room to talk bitch make up whatever fucking lies you want they ain't gonna fuck the whole ground
My dog is right next to me bro like right here if he bark in is he
Fighting with me like I've had him for fucking ever the entire time. I've been streaming like seven years
Get the fuck out of here. Where was your kid when you were smoking meth in the car and you got arrested bitch
them all that how you want to be in south and put it in the fucking door
Nurse haha, yeah, I work as a nurse
I've never been
Personally, I mean
I'm not gonna make army. I don't know anything about but your dog was fine. I don't know anything about you though
This is the first time I've ever
Maybe yeah, my dog is in trouble
He looks he looks terrible
Thank you, that should be your dog. Oh, I can't have a dog, but that's a cute dog. I love I love to
Good boy, man. I love my life right there
Isn't this
Did he change his name or is this
Is he sick a dirty good ghost, you know sick
Okay, I'm a joker to be honest with you. I didn't know I wasn't paying I thought I was joker jokers in a beanie
Joker gained 200 pounds
Psyche
Know I'm bad. I'm sorry. Yeah, what the fuck bro. You said that shit. No, like you fucking said that shit and
goddamn
I'm he said something bad on my stream last night, so I owe him a little shit
Give him some more shit
Well, no one time with you one time
He was like I don't know if you can hear me right now
But one time he was like he was like I guess he was on stream
But he didn't know he's on my stream when he was sitting there like he likes playing politics dude
You won't you are without was that was I was literally has no psyche has no problem
Like talking shit about me, but he'll bite his tongue with other people do
It could it's easy
You will talk shit about me and say whatever no maybe you deserve it, but you bite your tongue for others bro
And that's facts bro
And that's fine. That's what you want to do. That's okay. What do you agree with that signal? What do you do?
That's so good. We should talk about
All your volunteer work all your community service
Well community service being a POS
Bro, he won't let me watch that fucking hat. It must smell like fucking embers math pipe
Or beard
I can't do a beer. It just smells like fucking like dead bugs will be fucking
Bro, why are you so slow? I know you're muted something like when you talk to you like literally
Are you thinking about what to say because if you are you take that long to actually think about what you're saying you were kind
I got to say you're you're slow
It takes you like 20 seconds to respond and then like you respond about shit
We said 20 seconds ago like why are you thinking about it for that long?
Alright, I'm done. I'm done. Okay. I don't think you can hear us. Say are we muted now or you hear us are you ignoring us?
I think he's ignoring us thumbs up if you're thumbs up for your dumb dumb
Why is amber saying why is amber saying that you beat your dog LD?
She's high on math. I beat my dog. Well my dog. Hey, let me answer the question
If I told my dog
My dog is treated better
You ain't gonna beat nothing out of me, bro. I would beat you into a wood pulp if you a wood pulp
See, I told you don't like stop stop and you're not stop. Let's go Stig. I'm like an hour away from you
No, well, no, no, no, no, no pull-ups on my show. No pull ups. So
Yeah, and no pull down. Yeah, say no
No threatening. No threatening. You can have a banter, but not no threatening. I don't like it. Damn, you know
I gave him some credit though. I said 15 seconds. That was literally like 35 seconds after
And then he like fucking
I don't know. I think he has like a 45 second delay. It seems like he was sitting there for a long time.
What can you do? Siggi, Siggi, Siggi. I'm not ending another stream because you're being silly, okay?
Last time he was like, I don't know why you ended the stream just because I put up a picture of Amber in Shackles.
That's public info. She was arrested and it's public info.
Well, maybe he just doesn't give a fuck about it.
I don't know.
Don't put hands on it.
It's not a place for personal vendetta.
It's a show I don't give a lot of pictures on my show as an avatar. Yeah, I just think he could be he could be so deranged
Like I don't like when you say hi, I'll kick you. It's his show. Yeah, that's not that's not you are breaking TOS though
And it you are breaking TOS though
How am I breaking the terms of purpose you on permission to look it up photo as your profile?
It's a public. It's a public image. It's from a public court room
Images of people getting like fucking kill. I'll be you're not gonna post that on the YouTube. Are you that's different getting getting injured
That's not different hypothetically. It's the same thing. Why if I put her mug shot up here? It's the same thing
It's the public it's public info
Okay, well, this is not this is not the place
I'm giving you a chance to respond verbally you don't have to do with it the picture doesn't prove anything it doesn't do it
All it all it does is like, you know, it's just only his picture. That's that's my rule
Okay, it doesn't need to be an argument. You do it. I do do I have to I have to ban you. Okay?
Okay, so
Respect the show. Okay, I don't think it's that interesting either. We don't really give a fuck
Yeah
Do you have a personal vendetta, maybe you guys you and her should argue in your engine
Sick are you okay? Why do you have the look on your face sick?
Okay, I mean I can't take it you're driving crazy sick. I can't wait 20 minutes for response, please
it's ridiculous okay sorry guys i mean geez is he gonna sit there this is sort of just like for
like forever we're just like staring at space okay god okay yeah just talking talking to chat
you can do that so um yeah i mean she's sick
yeah i don't like it's like i
I don't like to look keep overemphasizing the rules because it just brings attention that people just won't like to break them
But you know, I am kind of under attack right now. So I try to try to stay within all the guy. I don't like you being so nice
Psyching I'm nice
Yeah, you're way too fucking nice you let people back up let people walk over you. It's like I'm for I'm forgiving
I'm forgiving because I think there's there's some good in people and it's okay to be forgiving. Yeah, but
But I do what
Other people talk it's not like it's not like they were in the same room. It is there's danger. It's gonna beat me up
I can talk to people we're all across
Different places across the country and you know just talking over the phone or video. Hey, baby
Okay, we got spunky
Hi hi
It's funky. Oh
The cute dog
Thank you. Yeah, he's a beauty. So I gotta find him a new one. He's so abused
That looks like a fast fucking dog. Yeah
He's the right. Yeah, he's the right side in Florida. Yeah
Yeah, dude, my boy right here
She's a nurse too spunky. He's a nurse too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I was telling her before. Okay. I'm missing. Sorry.
Oh, it's kind of warm in here tonight. Yeah, I love I love nurses like so it's summer. They do God's work.
Let's see what's going on. Hey everybody. Yeah. So yeah, my
You know, we had to deal with some nurses last year. My dad got sick. He had these Filipino nurses. He was like
You know, it was a really bad time, but he was there were very
very
Compassionate and friendly and here I am here. I am everybody
Finally
Let me go get another year for Gotti. Let me go get
You did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you did, you
All right without the mustache. I know dude
I'm a worn out man. I'm worn out from the from the beach today. She promised you were gonna wear a hat
Who did
No, don't take the kid's helmet, dude. Come on.
AHHHHHH!
What are you doing?
Let the kid have his helmet. Don't start a fucking war over nothing.
I'm here to buy a special for Justin, so they can, like, bang heads together.
Mongoloid madness. No, come on. That's rude. Yeah, that's rude. Mongoloid. Jesus. Come on Steph. I hurt my feelings
I want a public forum. I want a public forum. Exactly. Poor ghost. Yeah, I did a 23 and me and I have Mongolian beef.
Don't ever take it for a Mongolian beef. You might flip out.
No, no good. Hey. Hey, these are free jokes. Oh, all right
God just got a rib shot for me you guys not gonna come up
I'm sick of seeing these two fucking guys all the time. I know Justin's like freaking out tonight
He don't want to get on cam. All right, you then you do it for me then. All right even out this fucking
I'll turn it off now. He's ready. No, she has to eat it off
The race goes way off
It's always way off on this panel for some reason yeah, I feel like I'm watching legally blond
Yeah
You know fell in love with you today ray, you know ray. I know I know yeah, then he was like
Calling me a man cuz I wouldn't talk to him. Oh really? Yeah, it's pretty much. Yeah, that's that's his reaction to most women
Like she's obviously a woman and I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'm a dude
Oh, no, he said she looked like first.
He said she looks like Flirty Diamond.
It looks like Flirty Diamond.
Oh, I was just.
Yeah, a little bit.
But no, no, come on.
And I'm so sorry for saying that.
That's what I apologize.
I don't think she has a captain, Winky, dangling over there.
No, no, I think you've got it.
I think you got both of her legs.
Now you guys figured out Justin. He really is in a man. That's why he's with me
Justin we have something to talk about please join please join
He's into the old Einhorn thing. Yeah. Yeah
I can see him run into the shower just burning his clothes and fucking crying
Why he must be burnt like a lobster then
Okay, one second guys
What do we do the end of the panel again, I did it. Oh, oh LD got the kick
Yikes
Oh, that's cool how much 25 hit it again. That's not like shit. We got the
LD you've been gone. You should thank y'all D for that. Thank you. Thank you and thank whoever gave it
What happened?
No, no you somebody paid
Are you?
No, it works that way here
Yeah, is it possible to know who paid?
No
That's why I was afraid to like make it like lower than that because
It's a thousand bucks. I know kicking the taking me I'd be like now. No, it should be more. It's actually should be 50
Well, even if I get kicked, I'd have to be backstage, but I could let the guest run the
I don't know how much math goes for, but
With those handcuffs on when she paid?
Actually, I know nothing about it. I shouldn't be off my mouth today.
I might be next now.
Swanky, just so you know, if she does kick me to 25,
you can buy me back for 25.
Can I buy it back?
I don't know how much math goes for.
Someone someone
Someone banned Alex for 24 hours for 25 and then Alex bought himself out for a hundred dollars
Dollars for 24 hours
You're worth a grand to me. No, that should be like 10 minutes or like 30 minutes at least
It should be like a hundred dollars for 24 hours like he
No, I think it's I think that's too much. It was just like, you know, it's like
They really hate they hate them that much they'll be willing to pay it, you know, would you pay a thousand for Justin?
No, good. Yeah, that's the right answer. I pay a thousand
I would let's say I would let's take on but he's just killing the panel because I asked him a question
He's sitting there silent and then he just says something dumb. I can't take it like I know things. Oh, thank you
Hey, nobody asking and they're not asking for him. I guarantee
Well, Joe shipply and
Obviously, I don't know if they're there in cahoots or something like that. That's crazy. Okay. He left okay
But I say let's come back later sick. It's not the right time you were
Asked you a question you took 20 seconds answer. I can't he makes me depressed
I'm depressed as well
I want to light his beard on fire that little shit that he has under this what beard
Defend himself, can you ask a question then wait 40 seconds, please?
What I
Say we're all hanging out with you. See are you gonna answer? Hello. Are you there?
We could do like the spelling before Matt yeah, okay
What
I gotta be I gotta be honest and I don't mean to be rude, but you make Alex a fucking genius
Math. Oh my god. Don't be mean. Come on. Math. Support math. All right. I'll stop. I'll
Sick, how you doing? By the way, I'll answer you in 40 seconds. I'll expect the answer
Time tells how you're doing
You're kidding me. I'm tells all that's how you're doing. I just said how are you doing?
You're doing
Are you talking who let me speak in your language? Oh
The fuck are
You sign language
Talking to you. Okay. That's not sign language. I tell you what the next thing I do is I'm like, yeah
That's not sign language, and I think that's offensive to people that are dad
I think you're offensive to people on the panel. So I don't want to wait a minute. Yeah, sir
People are deaf, people are deaf, and people don't wait a minute to answer because that is the only language that they can actually speak.
Now you're talking, I'm excited, go ahead.
Now you're excited, let's go.
You want to crack your jokes, you want to wear your like, you know, 150 dollar eyelashes.
What are you talking about?
That's okay.
And I respect your right to do that.
I'm the only one talking to you, you dumb dumb.
You know, but.
And don't talk shit about my eyelashes by the way.
I was translating the shit
$75 by the way, you know what I'm we were hot. I'm saying what I'm saying stands
You know honesty
Fuck you're saying I gotta be honest brother. I'm trying to be if you don't know what I'm saying then that's your problem
You should be listening
Sorry
Nah, that's good. I'm not gonna fuck
Who the fuck are you talking to you? I know you I know you I know you must jump on her because you felt like good
But you I know you were actually more mad at me
Talking to you
I'm pretty sure I was talking to you. What do you want to talk about?
I'll be right back. I'll be right back. Okay. God. We're talking about my we talk about my
I don't think I don't find an importance and in what I'm saying and eyelashes
Then why the fuck would you break then? Why would you even why are you here?
You're saying are you bringing it up?
I can't hear to talk to psyche you guys are just arguing
What do you want to talk to me? Well, we're not me now
This woman over here, you know, she wants to say her things.
She wants to say her things and God bless her, that's her right.
And I'm going to say my things as well in response to God bless me, that's my right.
And I just want to see my friend
You guys are just being weird and hating and I'm just here to see my friend
I'm just here to chill out with my boy right
Okay, when I see you say I'm glad you're here. This guy is this guy right here. This ghost guy, whatever this guy is, you know, like, uh, yeah, let's let's have it. Well,
Let's say let's put it like that. Let's do a psyche psyche. This guy. This I'm not saying no names. I'm just saying. No, don't don't.
This guy over here you're expletive fucks you're
Have plenty of things
Can you say it quickly, please
You guys would rather just talk about
Let's let's run that bitch dog. Never mind. We'll see you later. Say it's not it's not the time right now
You're just droning on and on about not even smart enough to even crash out on I've been smart enough to have the conversation
You can't even have the conversation. I mean, I'm honestly concerned. I feel like I'm making fun of someone that has a disability
I don't think he's on drugs or anything now. I feel bad
I
Just approved
Like God
Is long look how long the cigarette is it goes all the way off screen. It's
that is a pretty sweet heart
oh what though
I heard what you said
you little sexy piece
look my eyes look
accentuated because I'm drunk
and my eyes are barely open
and I'm gonna be like
great I don't know what you saw
can you not give us the crazy eyes when you do though
exactly
Let's see and which one of you is most likely crazy eyes all night like two more two months
What the fuck happened to God you get kicked out he had to know he had to go
I'm afraid of Adam and Steve. He wants to go beat up stage. He could defend you if he really cared about it
I think he just leaves, you know, yeah, I mean I have to sometimes I defend psyche you can believe how
Hard that is so I mean, I'm sure God could defend you
I mean, I like really like no offense is that beautiful?
He doesn't know we saw I wouldn't feel so evil if we're not evil
I would feel so bad if I were seen like somebody's like Joe's like a bismol. I like God like I maybe I'm
Joining panels. I'm a
Joe Joe, I've been caught
Thank you, sweetheart
I don't even know what that word means. I'll be honest. I mean, I think the abyss is like hell. And so it's like
Were you the one at the beach earlier spunky?
Oh, damn. Are you looking real good? You were in a debate spunky earlier. How'd you do? I was at the beach. Yeah
I was on
Sorry
They went I agree nice to meet you sweetheart. I thought that might have been you
Thanks sweetheart. It's nice to meet you
Oh, that's too far.
She's a boyfriend.
He has a boyfriend.
Say ma'am.
Should I call Joe Muffin?
I mean, what would you prefer?
Well, see, now that's attack.
That's actually rude.
You called me sweetheart.
I like beat up.
Now I can come up tomorrow like beat him.
He's like, oh, he called me Muffin Gates.
He called me little Muffin Gates.
Look at Joe didn't call me muffin. I'm I'm gonna I'm counting down from 10 and if you don't take Joe out
25 bucks or whatever it is
Did you really?
Yeah, $35
I think it's 25 for an hour
There's for 24 hours inside 25 hours
I think that's a new rule. Oh my god, I love the invention my feet because it's got you in the chat right now
And I'm asking honestly how much to rub them 20 35 45
But you're a foot fetish
No, when I say I'll rub them I meant I'll rub them with my tongue who said that
I was going to say that. I knew you were going to say that to me.
I always fuck everything up. I'm just trying to fucking
know that I had to go and do all that.
They're offering me money to rub my feet.
But don't say they, they are not.
You say Joe is offering you that shit.
I'm just teasing him.
Gotti and Justin have a thing about my shoes.
Psyche, are you offering money to lick them hogs?
I
that's why she's my ex here
I fucking doing that
Girlfriends in you, but you know what I'll give you some respects like you've had more men
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Oh, you know when you look by the way, spunky every time you look into the fucking camera and you yell Justin
I think that there's somebody's on the panel
Justin's that'll come dingle if you come up on panel
Yeah, I mean, you know, I didn't show you my dick but
Oh
Hey, no Joe Joe because oh yeah, someone made a dumb joke like about 40 diamonds
So Joe's in love with flurry diamond, right? Would you say with the anal beads Joe?
It's a play along I'd say yeah, I'm in love with it. Okay. Yeah
You said you're power, right? I'm done
Fucking degenerates, I'm tired hearing about it. I can deal with sucky
Who are you talking? Thank you. Thank you. See why thank you boy. He goes. Oh
What are you asking ask the question again?
Well, I wasn't listening to generate behavior. I was actually fucking almost vomiting, but go ahead. What were you saying?
Generation X
Suck it. I'm having a terrible time understanding you. Oh, I'm having a very hard time over here psych
I'm having a very hard. Can you please repeat it? Well, then please I didn't fucking hear the question. Please ask me again
Why
Joe I told you I told you no means no Joe
All right fair enough. I
Mean yeah, Joe Joe you a crystal was saying last night she was saying
She's a you psyche. She's like you said you said I use Chris. Yeah, Crystal Marie. She said you look like
You you said I looked like Kim
and I was like
And I was like when are wet and she's like you said I look like Kevin and she was so bad
I'm always sad. I'm sad kid. It's not my girlfriend. She's even said she has a boyfriend. She's my friend
So I'm not funny you guys talk about him. That's fair. You can talk to her like that
Just say it to her face when she's here
Crystal that's what I was saying when I was a crystal said
Okay, I won't say anything. Well, I'm gonna invite you sagging in November
Like a dumb dumb last night she crashed the fuck out. Yeah, I do remember it actually
Crystal went off on me last night. Yeah, she fucking went off. She crashed out
she thinks you deserve
No, she's saying I she was saying I called her things that I never called her like she said exactly
No, she went on like a
diluted
Like schizophrenic crash out like it wasn't even a good crash out
Like she was just crashing up about like fucking weird-ass shit that no one said no one claimed that she does she went off on one
I was like, it wasn't summer solstice. I guess there was some weird energy in the atmosphere or something
It had to be the song because it wasn't the moon. I know one was fucking it was a network
There's some reason never weird all being good fuck
Crystal Marie is if you're gonna crash. I'll just make it a little really tiny bit
I'm not gonna even talk about it because she was getting mad at me and say I said things I never said so
So she'll appear like beetles juice well beer. Yeah, like Beetlejuice. Hey, did we set her name twice? Don't do it again
You speak it three times
Don't say it I can't I can't tell you how many times that it's actually I don't say I don't think it. Oh look my friend
Big Nisha's here. Big Nisha. Hi darling. Yeah, we said it three times now
Okay
Be careful using my hand signs for they're dangerous. Okay. Well, you
Three times so disappear arrow, Darryl Darryl. Go away. Is that one see gone guys?
No, you just made a pop-up on panel. Oh
No, I'm just kidding.
All right, y'all, you tricked me.
I'm having a nice weekend, baby Nisha.
How are you?
You're gonna come on panel.
You're welcome.
Hey, everybody.
Guys, let's see.
Oh, so yeah, so I restarted the stream.
It's probably a good thing.
I think it's gonna keep building up tonight.
Things are really cool. The panel is really cool, isn't it?
This is a good panel, I like this panel.
It's 330 in the end, it's not going to build up so easily.
Well, sometimes it gets popular.
Probably in the morning, there was like 40, 50 people.
There was 50 people.
It's much earlier, for sure.
I remember that.
Nice, Bunky.
Hi.
Who's that one?
Hi, that place over in Monica.
That guy.
How's it going? Getting a kill?
He's banned. He's banned.
Mr. Big Types is banned.
Oh.
Big.
That was him I liked his I like what he performs but that he gets
We're well, wait, wait guys. What was the song?
He's saying a song for like two hours. I said, you know the song it was like a beetle song
He usually does a rap song
Now we had Beatles last night brother
What was the Beatles song? Do you know it goes?
It was
I'll see I don't know after I'm on my phone right now. I would look it up. But yeah, it's awesome. I always I don't fucking know
But he's singing for two hours everybody and then he was like in the background singing we were all trying to talk and like
He eventually got mad. I put him back stage. He came back on and said the N word a bunch of times.
I saw him saying some weird shit to you, you know, the shower conversation or whatever.
I didn't understand what that was about.
Yeah, I don't know. It was just like, he was like, you want to make out with me?
Then he wants me to like take a shower and brush my, I was like, I don't even want to kiss you in the first place.
the
I tell him not to that boy went there as he fucking he fucking became like Peyton Manning
he fucking tossed that soap, Gary.
Oh god, what's moving?
Sorry, sorry.
That wasn't bad, Jail.
I always say I went to jail, I dropped the liquid soap in jail and just felt it running.
It's really hard to escape off the floor too, it took a long time to escape.
the
And he's like, oh shit, no, blah, blah, blah, this dude, this other dude, yeah, this other
dude's in jail.
He's like, ah, this other black dude.
All right, I'm not gonna drop the
You you fucking gay, why do you think? No, that's my girl. Why do you think they're on a men's side you gay?
You did that shit outside of jail
It's 2025 that's an offensive word
Yeah. Right. You're getting knocked out in twenty. You can say dumb dumb as you guys want. I gave you permission. Yeah, that works. I like that. I like dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb
Oh, it's not a census to them at all psyche. We found your group name the candy crew. There we go
No, it's a psyche person. I would
Don't start with say it good work. It works like and this is psyche verse. Are we just the psyche's name name name your own universe?
What's up my psyche? I can't understand a fucking word. You're saying I'll be answered me. Thank you
That's what I think it should be called
Psychoverse
Joe we don't hear
Okay, I say oh, I say we just entero
You're your guffamise. Oh, I say you want to be you want to hang out here? I want I want a tarot reading that's just you know
I would love an animal
Hey, I got dips. Thank you. All right front of the bus for me for once in life. All right
Yeah, here you go. You're the you're the Rosa Parks of
I'm the Rosa Park of psyches fucking bush right now
Okay, well, that's it the bag. You're the Rosa Park of
Kara wait, I must pronounce that it's not carrot
Psychic reading. Yeah, I'm doing a couple. How do you pronounce it? I'll get your car. It's tarot
Taro. Taro. Taro. The last last last T is silent. Okay.
Taro. Taro. Taro. Taro. Taro. Taro. Taro. The last last last T is silent. Okay.
Okay, we have three flowers. Oh, she got it. That was good. I'll give her one. I'll give her that one
Three of flowers that was good. That was good spunky
and
Three of flowers is about teamwork. So this is about coming together. It's Jeremy. She gotta help you a passionate way with people
You know, not sexual passion, but it's like in it in the something that gets you excited and
I'm talking to Isaiah.
I'm talking to Joe Bar-Azeo.
Isaiah, it says, the three of flowers
reminds you of the important teamwork, cooperation,
and good communications.
You can't accomplish everything by yourself.
Ask for support to bring your creative vision to life
and help you plan to reach the full potential.
And then you have this night of hedgehogs.
And so this guy is actually the night of panicles.
OK, so this is either.
You know someone coming to you with the some kind of offer rushing to you with it
Or it's that you out driving your car and going somewhere with this money offer you has a little
His little rucksack I guess on his back. So it's a lizard from a from Alice in Wonderland
Okay, he's a knight. So and he's also the slowest. So I might be waiting
You might be waiting for a little bit for something but it will come or you might keep someone waiting
But I'll tell you I'll tell I'll give you the interpretation here. It says so hedgehog. Okay
It says the night of hedgehogs is, it says the night of hedgehogs is a
industrious and diligent as Bill the lizard who makes, who risked it all trying to dutifully
To dutifully soar say go to the see the white rabbit's house after Alice
Grows so gigantic portions the Knights of Hedgehogs reminds you to stick to your routine work and
Focus on the details work hard and focus on the
Well, they're well said buggy. Wait. Thank you. I'll cut them off. Yes. Yeah, I like your tattoos spunky. That was very well said
Thank you, you know
That was it. Yes, that was it. Oh
Yeah, I appreciate it. You're welcome. You're welcome. It just looks like it just looks like, you know
looks like it's a secure routine and
It'd be it you're working hard
But it's also like is working with other people too, and they're also both the both fire
So there's a lot of fire there. So there's something you're really passionate. I don't want to do it a little fire
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Are there any advice to maybe sleep in his truck instead of the tent?
Oh
No gosh, come on
It's never it's never got to leave the car when uh before can't when the car is available
The woods try and scare me they they made an attempt it was valid it didn't scare
Couple of my cousins just went fucking
did like this crazy lap around the house to try and scare me and pop out of the house.
That's, that's, that's, it did, it did not work.
That's pretty funny.
I mean, it would be very hard to scare somebody though dark in the middle of the woods. Yeah
Yeah, it's Harry Harry clap I say I say it's been flexing on my show since its first appearance, you know
It was all you ask for it
of the
death of the
Ah, you know, if I say anything about nuts, it's going to come out gay.
I can't.
You should tell, you should tell Spunky that you're, you're a St. Patrick's Day story.
I say.
Why?
Well, why you tell everybody anyway.
I never heard it.
I never heard it, please.
Yeah, what happened?
I never heard it as well, Psyche.
Okay.
Okay, so on St. Patrick's Day, he got a little inebriated and a limo pulled up to the club
guy walks out and
He just tried making out with a guy one time. He decided a few days later. He didn't like it, but he tried and
Don't you add those few days later and like I'm fucking sitting there pondering in my room like man
Did I like that stash? Did I like five o'clock shadow rubbing on you? Oh?
no it was not that thank you oh no yeah for two days you just like sat in a
room and pondered
uh without question later that night i decided no i'm
I'm not gay. Well, not even
Yeah, you guys this is you know, you're big niche in the chat. This is a big niches husband
They her and I have been together for a good amount of years now, I
Love her. I really love her. I'm this way. I'm not the father of no now
Boy, I tell you
Ignition is like 500 pounds
Have you met have you met
No, I have not met spunky. Where are you from spunky spunky is from the west coast
Volter location
or personal information for you, if you're a taxi.
This is an undisclosed location.
Undisclosed.
I'm in a basement in New York City.
I'm going to blink twice, letting you know I need help.
Nisha, the nail on eye from Louisiana.
Unscrews location, her boyfriend's bedroom with her apart.
That was a silly fan.
That's a lie.
You're not in a basement right there in your line.
In Mexico.
It's about central air.
Thank you.
Mortal Kombat.
Very nice and media.
Have you met Nisha before?
I have not.
Oh, she's my darling, I tell you. I love her so much
She's a writer in psych is chat. Yeah, yeah, I got brought here by my boyfriend too
And then I I have now fallen in love with psyche and I'm in here all the time now. I
Know that yet like me
Hey, who was the one who?
Her name is not Queefa.
Shut the fuck up.
Yeah.
That's a beautiful name.
Yeah, Queefa's amazing.
The Shaquifah is a cousin of Big Nisha
I've done that hurry there. You have met her. Yeah, well, we've had a lot of people love her
But so she's a cousin of Big Nisha and
Nisha Nisha and I dated for a while. We're no longer together
But don't know and I like don't know
Good boy. I'll tell you
I
Compliment you look like that blonde ashes from Reno 911 like that blonde
Um
Good-looking girl the show so yeah
Compliment I won't be rude I'm backing them up. That's I don't know all night long. I've just heard about how I look like
Transgendered women and different things. I don't know. What's in here?
She's that third diamond is the transgender like the local transgender here
Well, someone said it, well, someone said it, I don't
Well, if you know fruity trance, does that make you gay when you call her gorgeous?
Does it make me gay? I am gay, like
No, not you, not you. Well, I mean, I guess theoretically, because she identifies as a she, so does that make you lesbian?
No, but this is an actual woman. Spongebob is an actual female.
And it only works, yeah.
I mean, that just wins against what he does.
Yeah, it's funky.
That just makes you straight.
You're fine.
But if a guy said fruity is attractive,
knowing that it's a dude, it's gay.
Don't call us fruity.
Come on.
and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love her, and we love
Crafts that gumbo. Oh, there's no comparison
Bro, yeah, let her let her let her be big and be good at cooking. Yeah
He crashed that gumbo
Like really make this guy put a fucking sum over him
Here you go.
Fucking disgusting, now fucking sit up here
trying to look funky and I can't fucking hear you.
That is the worst looking thing ever.
Grow up, man.
Put it close.
You grow up, I've been the fucking middle of the woods.
Why the fuck am I gonna have a shirt on?
Just because you're dressed in woods,
I mean you can't wear clothes.
I could wear a shirt if it was a fucking night in the breeze out here.
No, Joe doesn't want to get excited, so he doesn't.
Yeah, no, right, no shit.
Giving him an awkward boner here.
At least the cab are off.
No one will wear that.
Fuck, no.
Why am I not going to show off my hairy beastlyness?
And also, I need the camera.
So you guys could witness if some bear or some crazy fucking animal
comes slaughter me in the fucking...
Well, you know, you know, he will end the stream immediately. Yeah, I'm not having anybody. Oh, no, I like I like I will like
The chat how much to beat Justin on cam
Oh, she's laying on her bed now. I'll give you a hundred out there join your fans. I give like 50 bones
I will do it for free. Oh, you better
Let's do it for me. Yes
Only Spongebob fans
Joe has his only fans and he has two fans. I have what I'm wait. I have no butt got
About your only fans Joe
Yeah
You on cam not you're not your wee wee like to beat you up do it
That will be the domestic violence slide.
Then Big Bubba is going to shrub like, oh.
That cost extra?
What are you doing?
He's going to have to be blood.
OK, no, that's too violent for my stream.
I know.
I wouldn't hurt him.
Yeah.
We're actually really good together.
I would never hurt him.
I can't.
I feel the love.
I really can.
Yeah, I love you.
I was going to lay one on him and say I was going to beat him up with my lips.
It's like,
she's just your feet.
God, he said she showed her feet.
No, you know,
Oh, did I show her feet?
Yo, he's missing out foot finder dog like
Do you get a special sense of attention being the only woman in this panel? Oh
No, I mean I get enough attention in real life that it doesn't matter but I
Find that I like the company of men more than women
i don't know maybe in like past lives or whatever i've probably been a man before
i have a definite sense of femininity but i my jokes and my humor are all dirty man stuff so
i love it like where you just did the military or why do other women your age think of you i would
say about you
Oh, well, people in general just think I'm like a very nice kind person, but
Yeah, but I have this other side of me that I like bring out on the internet and
I mean you're experiencing normal me
So
Like what do you what do you think makes that site so wild and exciting?
Oh, I don't think it's wild and exciting. I just think that's just what I'm like vibing on so I like to
Hang out with guys on the internet and talk
And what is your boy about that?
He's in the other room doing some work, so he doesn't really care, but he brought me in here
All the other guys inside are in the room right now are gay, so he doesn't care
He doesn't he doesn't care. We're like super super secure like I could be
On the internet and he would trust me like
I bet your boyfriend's a nerdy little bitch
Justin, you're a nerdy little bitch, they said.
Yo.
Bitch, boy, friends, get up and be a little punk.
No, I think he's a stud. He has to be a hyperbolic.
No, he has to be twin.
He looks just like me, but a dude.
It's weird, right, Goddy?
I feel like he's a skinny white dude with...
He's probably got just packet, or he's a fat white dude.
Not fat.
He's not fat.
Either way, packet.
He's not fat, but...
Yeah, he's not only packing, but well skilled.
It's what it is. I don't think he makes a lot of money.
I feel money talk show that money
I know we're just fucking around on chat, but there's literally no amount of money that can get me my man
I think that's the I can respect that that's fair. That is yeah, like there isn't
There's
Dude, I agree agrees. Yeah, when you find that like
When I look I've been married a bunch of times. I'm old, you know
Masters our relationships
Relationships so I finally met somebody that I like really really really fucking vibe with and it's been a year and a half
And it's been amazing and I would never
Do anything in a job?
Yeah
three. That's what I wanted to
40. Wow. No, you're not old.
baby. I mean, you're not old,
but you're old. I've been jokingly
and calling him quattro. You
know, quattro. What does that
mean? Quattro. Four. Oh, okay.
you retard. You know what
We literally landed out for you and you still was like, I don't know what that is.
What the fuck?
Uh, side note, side note, will you, can we see your arms, the, the tats?
Yeah, you can. I have a lot of them. Uh, I have this one.
Do you have any names of exes? No, no, but I have Justin's initial on me
I do I do I'm gonna show you so I have okay, this one is for my best friend he passed
Yeah, it's a lotus flower, you know for a general life, and then you know what sugar soul like do the dead stuff. Yeah
He was really cool. He was a gay gentleman since I was 12 and he was 38.
I have a... I'm 38.
I have leopard spots around the world.
You want a 38 year old?
I want flowers.
Is that from a deceased?
No
It's a go this goes only like up my back and stuff, but I have that I have
Yeah, my goat is fucking awesome. I'm looking at her nipple
Okay
So if you want it to be like you're in your in your bra, we're gay
Well, if we want if she wanted to be out of her bra, I was
We got a lot of cleavage and I didn't get an erection because I'm so
Where's his gay men
That's good. I love gay men. Yeah, we're all like touch dudes, but you know, yeah, we're super gay
Especially Joe Joe's like leader of us. The leader of the guys. Yeah
Exactly gay queer gay command. Do you believe that's funky? Do you believe what he's saying?
Who's the spunk bastard?
Well, Joe's been gay for a while
Oh, well, whatever you said man, but I've seen that video
He's your neighborhood gay guy
Yes, why can't I compliment a good lady's good looks what I didn't call gay, bro
I know that that's the internet for you, right because we got to be gay
Because we're gonna be because we were talking about her nipple and I wasn't thought I wasn't complimenting for me
Like a sexual standpoint. He's like wow
I can appreciate it
I have beautiful nipples
I don't believe Joe, I think you're missing the gay train because we're trying to
Any through a 50 cent piece on this. So have you heard of the backstage situation like we can go backstage?
Oh my god
What are we talking about?
We're gay men, so we're just like gonna be like girl
Yeah, I'm not gonna, you know, I'll tell you I'll tell you how nice they look, you know, yeah
I'm going to bed
She flies
I don't know her like I just saw her in the chat earlier and
When I basically want her to give birth to you because
I
That's a mommy issues right there
He's gonna just suck in the queef and live on that
Yeah, I'm a queef farmer
Well, Shaquiffa Jackson is a queef instructor.
Oh, yeah.
We work with Amber.
Well, Shaquiffa worked with Amber for many years.
Oh, now it's all the gay guys.
Yeah.
It looks like we're getting a start, right?
It's so fucking cool.
I've been in the middle of fucking woods.
Give me a break.
I can't help it.
Nobody's here.
Ah, yeah.
Give me my...
You're brought up all late, motherfucker.
the
You were you were the nine squirrels. You stole nine squirrels nuts
Joe's not black is he
What I said something about you and nine squirrels nuts
Yeah, I thought I ain't ever he's actually better than most of you come by
Yeah
I guess I don't know because it would be a great insult if I knew who the fuck you
I mean, no, I mean not a
Polynesian Islander, that's
Well, yeah, I'm German it's in German last name
I am Nigerian
that's what I want to make rogue is soup out of your flesh
that's what I want to make
that's going to last you for like a good 6 months because there's a lot of
soup based in soup
if yes me
and how much would you call it
why would you call my soup
I will call it stew gay
gay stew
stew gay
Okay, and how much will you charge for this two of you?
Maybe four five bucks you'd be probably like a hot dog vendor on a street cart type shit, you know
Yeah, it's like we're not talking Gordon Ramsay restaurant like you know, no, no
He's just selling that the flesh
Where's for 499?
who can get a chicken salad with grilled chicken for 499 Tuesdays have good competition against you where we're the father
Grilled chicken for 499 liar. They don't know is it where I didn't I get there's a taco bill
No, no chicken, but organic chicken where I live. Oh, yes. Yep. There's a place called and
Yeah, and grill and
They sell
salad with organic chicken for $4.99
and guess what, I have one in...
It's gotta be salad in like a three ounce fucking souffle cup.
No, no, no, no, no, it's in a genuine thing, no.
How could they possibly afford a fucking salad?
When I saw the billboard as I was driving, I said, wow, $4.99 salad with the chicken?
They'll let us cost more to fucking get to the bulldozer.
I know, I don't know why they do it, but they're doing it.
Bullshit. Yeah. All right. Well, they're fucking
Hemorrhaging fucking money
People in and try not my business. I'm just the eater of the salad
That's that's my game you stop eating my fucking food's food, please. All right. Thank you. I appreciate that
Are we what are we not a gay panel?
the
You're eating and everything else in there that my steak needs to grow nice and strong and delicious
I need a cat first like fuck those cats. I'm fucking mm-hmm so tasty
Can we just be reasonable here with this legitimate question, right?
Do you think like alright everybody's eaten American nice shine like
American Chinese food, right? How many cats you look like you've had a little too much American Chinese food
Think about it, though, like how much do you think is that of you look like you're not fucking not the right meat
It's you get your general T. So's chicken
And is that really chicken?
Yeah, it's really chicken. Is it is it though? Is it I mean, you know prove it
But I mean even if it was like fake has chicken is probably is being is doing me a better fucking favor that is doing
I like her little toes they look like little chicken clothes. Thank you, Jim. I love you
I think that you're focusing on the cultural aspect of food and not the true pragmatic aspect
because whatever you're eating is not doing you any favors.
But I understand that I'm not a fucking healthy American with the fucking way I
Myself after I fucking find the butcher that's rely or whatever that's why exactly so cold early
You believe that whatever the fuck you're eating makes you more masculine
No, no, no, no, no, no makes you be like a man because you didn't say that
You say that I eat steak other than my steaks
I didn't say that made me a man. I said that makes you eating my fucking foods food and please stop doing that
So if I'm eating a fucking lettuce, so my steaks can eat their lettuce and I should healthy
Like what is the benefit of your steaks like you eating the steaks that it myself?
Cuz cuz it's feeding my my my meal correct, but I'm asking what is the benefit do you get out of that?
Because I
Enjoy eating steak. No, but not what are you? I didn't ask what you enjoy
That's the benefit is I in it's it beneficial would enjoy me
Eating steak. I didn't say there. Well, no
There's also the health benefit of all right
So if they don't have to give them artificial shit because less people ate fucking my food's food
Then I can get more natural healthy food
And it's right and what like have you looked it in the mirror? What do you look like?
what's it doing for you well nothing because i can't afford the stage did you keep eating my steak
fucking food and driving up the fucking prices so i can't eat fucking healthy organic natural
shit that i want to eat but look like like even if i what you eat lettuce every fucking day you
can still be fucking fat it don't matter favors like even if i were to eat all
You do you do understand right that yes, they have a beer gut from drinking
The rest of my body is completely cut, right?
Have you ever stepped in a tiny bit what is your body fat percentage?
Oh, dude, I don't f***** know, I mean, why would I pay attention to that and care?
Why don't fuck with me because you're so focused on my job because I'm a landscaper.
You're so focused on what social nutrition is doing for your body, right?
What nutritional fucking...
Okay, all right, so if you want to argue that you're somehow more muscular from eating fucking lettuce versus a protein diet,
completely fucking retarded. There is no question. You can have a higher muscle to fat content ratio,
but your muscular, your general health and your general physique...
It's gonna be a fucking twig that is completely male fucking tourists. There is no question about that
Look at babies like fucking the hippie fucking douchebags and the fucking vegans that
When was the last time you had a blood work panel actually
Was it last it wasn't last was it last week within the past week
No, I don't have high cholesterol, no I don't have high blood pressure, my uric acid levels
are fucking perfect, my sugar levels are fucking perfect, I don't have diabetes, right?
And when was the last time you had this body fat percentage?
My pulse ox, great, my fucking heart rate and...
Your body fat percentage?
Who cares?
All right, cool. Wait, wait, wait, wait, if I did my body fat percentage, right? I am lean everywhere
Oh, you are not. So that's your balance again
You are far from lean
What are we talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
What the fuck are you shitting me?
Alright, whatever. Doesn't matter
What is your body fat percentage on your lettuce healthy bullshit?
Unfortunately 12% at the moment. Unfortunately. I used to be under 10%
but unfortunately, it's 12% of you.
12% of you.
Poor baby.
You want his telephone number you want his job of employment? I mean you want to talk to
Like popped in here. You sounded like God for a minute, but I realized you turn all right. I got you, bro
God sounds like me
Credit card and shit. I mean I got black credit. So, you know anybody I got you guys. He's my boy. Oh
Dude, yeah, got his shit. God. He's the shit. I
Complain and I said you sound like
Like 55%
Fair enough and I will out
Lift you out run you
Hey, you all right body fat percentage and health unless you're morbidly fucking obese
Really doesn't mean anything over 25% makes you more believe these
There's no way the morbidly obese category
Well, how about you step at the scale and we find out otherwise we're just guessing I don't
What scale sir you got you guys might as well just just just just zip it down and just zip your pants measure dick's already
Just measure things measure your fucking dick's right. I'm better than you are fatter than you are got more less
Let's body percent fat and come on then I go
Oh
That's what's going on so you guys are having a little a pissing contest
One's athletic was not all I'm better than you
Hey gentlemen, you know where this conversation goes after this, right?
Once we establish who has the better body type,
then we start going into bank accounts.
Oh, how much money do you have?
I bet you I got more money than you.
Just that.
Bro, we know when these conversations go.
I stopped that already, bro.
I already fucking put my place on there.
I ain't got that bank account.
I got that fucking black one.
I got my dad's credit.
Yeah, actually, you know what? No, I got my mom's credit
My dad my dad's actually got decent fucking credit. I got fucking capital one. I
Have capital one too
What's the first what's the first couple of what's the first 16 numbers on your own on that on that capital one card?
the first
One seven one seven when they turn off slaves
Yeah, and now what I want you to do is flip the card over right flip the card over and I'll read me the thing
Where it says CVV number. It should be three numbers. What does that say?
And just read me the expiration date just for just to see if you're still good, you know
all of the
the
Darnell Carter, is that with two L's or one L? Darnell, is that with two L's or one, oh two?
Can I be, alright. Hey, Darnell Carter. Nice to meet you. My first name is Stay. My last name is Tert. Nice to meet you.
Very nice to meet you.
He's not dark enough for that name. I'm just saying.
I'm pretty sure that's not his real name.
I'm calling bullshit on the name. The card number
Also, I'm just saying they're repeating from memory in that cadence. How many of those numbers are right into their order
This guy has money on his card anyways, you know, you have the number and like the
What's up motherfuckers you got a double digit credit score
What's up motherfuckers?
I got the triple gorgeous baby, it's a butter.
Hello, fuckers.
How are you summer?
What's up, summer?
What's up, fuckers?
You know, you mean love me?
Apparently my body fat content's up, that's what's up.
Very hot.
What?
How are y'all talking about body fat?
What the fuck are y'all talking about?
I just jumped here on this conversation.
They're talking about lean bodies fat bodies step on a scale bodies
Summer I want to know that question please have the Italian flag on one ass cheek and I have the Cuban flag on the other
the
You throw in fucking pasta meatballs and fucking subs everywhere, bro
And then and whatever type of Cuban dish they make right
that's the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
To be fair, well, I just came up to say hey fuckers. I'll be back later
She was probably at the no Kings protests during the run. Oh God
One thing I love about summer it's like $20 you can get like a tattooed like a billboard or an asshole
Like you got an invention you made like I'm selling t-shirt
Remember we'll get a tattoo on our ass like
No fucking me
You know you'll be there's be
A
Beater
I'm down to talk Alex. You don't know. Let's run that bitch. Yo, I saw your fat ass
Crucible ghost don't ever talk to me again. You
You why can't you open your eyes when you talk bro, are you okay?
Dick don't forget the dick Alex you got to say dick
I got banned last night. I don't even know how I'm up here actually that's a good argument
I don't give a fuck. What would you want? No, I got banned last night for life. I don't even know how I'm up here
You're good. Why are you talking to me?
That's
your ghost
I was nice to him earlier tonight. Damn. He had to start off in Calibra's hint. He didn't make it to me though
Ghost you should have crashed the fuck out goes I swear to God you should have crashed down
You was way too quiet when he was up here. You was way too quiet. He was spazzing on you
It's okay. Who the fuck? Who?
You go never mind goes this slow never mind
No, you're talking to two different people
They gotta just hand it to you respect you better respect it you're
Say here the fuck you're talking to you or back top. You know better
Yeah, you fall back. You better know who you're talking to.
Yeah. Oh, no.
The thing is, you know who you're talking to and that's why you ain't getting crazy.
No, they try to fuck you fuck everything you do how many times have we debated how many times if I won
Check the score
You never do
That's one more
Zero
It's like 16 to 0, 15 to 0.
What are you talking about?
You're gonna try to win one now, but you're not gonna do it.
You can't. No, no, no. You're the one that's gonna have to do it.
You're the mister fucking debate king.
What's the three laws of logic?
But you don't know how to debate.
I don't debate I don't
Then shut the fuck up
But you still
Anything goes you like
Damn, it's so oh my gosh. Okay, you're fucking too stupid to have the conversation. There's my
You're too stupid to even have the conversation what conversation tell me what which conversation goes pick up
You small words you are too
literate and dumb
to have the conversation
Sir what the conversation about what's what sir?
The conversation about what sir what
Well, fuck it conversation about the conversation
I never
Yeah
I went again
I won again
Let's have it. Let's have the conversation
You got nothing bitch
I just told you the conversation about the conversation
Which would be if you were
Which I'll give you your argument
You should have said sir
Ghost, that's a meta conversation, but you're too fucking stupid to even have the conversation.
There's no conversation. Go on. Go on, brother.
Yeah, I'm not gonna go in again
It's a matter of
Conversation which I just explained to you
Shut the fuck up
I'm having a conversation about the conversation, but I don't want to meta-com
Conversation is a meta conversation is a conversation about the conversation with fucking
Conversation is something that you fucking geeks learn when we try to study fucking debating
No, you don't even know what the fuck you're talking about
I'm sorry to hear it conversation
Yeah, you don't even know what the fuck you're talking about
This is an easy boy
Meta conversation do not do not be wrong in the same sentence dickhead
I'll take any who else wants it
Met a conversation is on the conversation about the conversation. That's my point. Go ahead and prove me wrong
Let's run that bitch. No, you won't talk shit. Let's run it. You like that
Talk about it. Go ahead. I already brought him up. Oh, dude. No seagulls, but who else won't have any conversation about it
Nobody else won't see there was no stupid damage in regards to the conversation
I don't give a fuck what happened. I'm asking you. What is a meta conversation, sir? What in my metaphor?
What is a meta conversation? What is that? Do you even know the definition?
I just explained it to you six times.
Nobody gives a fuck what a meta conversation is.
You stupidly even have a conversation with a meta conversation.
What the fuck's going on here?
It sounds like a computer-
I have a conversation, let's run a little bit.
Make that big thing.
Can I let me ask a question?
I had a fucking answer question.
How many times, 15 times for you?
Fuckin no, bro. I was gonna have a meta conversation about his drinking habits right now
But it can't be I guess fuck you guys no no not you're talking about ghosts
Yeah, not you. No
Yeah, I don't know what you're drinking too much, you know, I was gonna talk about gosh real quick cuz he wants to have a meta conversation
Hey ghost if you listen it let's try to have a better conversation
If somebody says conversation one more time, I swear to God, we don't have a conversation conversation person. So what are we talking about? What are we, what are we talking about? Hopefully nothing you're talking about.
We're talking about Joe shit, please African American descent badly
of the
What's going on, Joe? How are you feeling, man?
You know what? We don't want to fucking hear every man is a word conversation.
So if a tree fell in the woods, the conversation even made a conversation?
it will be at that
that
Sure, but I might survive to your low body fat percentage apparently because you know I got more cushion so my legs
well he definitely called me fat
don't you let him call you fat like that
don't you fucking let him call you fat
it's okay I got my fucking dad
gut from fucking drinking
I earned that, I earned that fucking
drinking gut, fuck that
he's like fuck that I am fat
let him know
show me better shoulders in this fucking
that's a well deserved drinking gut
he been through a lot
He deserves that bad body, right now. Come on. Give me a better shoulder
Can you turn your cap?
Your shoulders look like balloons
That's that's what happens when you do hard manual labor every fucking day. They look like
That's not just jerking fucking dudes off
Yeah, bro. Yo, there's big body. Yo, he's stocking body as hell with like spaghetti arms. You are
they said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he said he
I
Stocky body with
You could do 10 push-ups 100%
you don't want to fall in your face
that's a very real possibility
I've been drinking this fucking dude
it's almost 5am
so that's probably what makes you think
in the middle of the woods
nobody gonna let me save me out here
impressive because they're not
12 o'clock
yo that's more than 12 hours of drinking
that's crazy
oh you talking about 12 o'clock tonight
or 12 o'clock this afternoon
that's why I told you I earned my fucking drinking belly baby
oh my gosh, dude, that's what 16 hours?
yep, 16 hours
that boy got that big belly on them little arms
Hey, they're super small arms. Well, it's who I was three. I don't know. Maybe I got five
It's 14 hours
I don't even understand how your language sounds English to me right now
I do
the
I don't want you to say that my voice so up here. Come on. Come down
You little the guy the guy that the guy that was drinking for but for hella hours. Um, is it for is it like before 40?
That really was 16 out going on 17 hours
Fuck a man right there
Oh, oh shit. Oh, yeah, you're right. I was doing that. He's a
retard man because I was like
Are you gonna cry tonight though
Yeah
So, yeah
Real man does cry every night
A real man who's crying every night needs therapy like real there
I say it things that he's too good for therapy. He doesn't I would I would never knock them in for crying in fact
Every night in there you got there's something going on
Yeah, but 100% you need to talk to somebody.
Oh, I don't need fucking therapy.
I'm too fucking bad as for therapy.
Like, now something's definitely going on in your life
where you really need it, like, and I will not
the therapy neither.
Like, there's nothing wrong with that.
Don't say a real man cries every night.
It doesn't get help about it.
That's a middle point.
He understands his vulnerabilities
and is able to channel them into strengths.
Thank you, sir. That's not how real fucking life works
that is outlight for us, thank you
thank you sir, but I say life works is
it's not willing to accept these vulnerabilities
so he doesn't necessarily make you stronger
but I say I just remain weak
because he's not willing to accept his vulnerabilities
so I'm going to show him
how to be strong
I can absolutely accept my vulnerabilities
but my mental state needs therapy
to get through other fucking traumatic issues
if you're not willing to accept how weak you are
if you're not willing to accept
How can you turn such weaknesses into strengths?
I, I, I don't, that, that doesn't correlate.
The fuck are we talking about?
Just because you understand how weak your, your, your, your vulnerabilities and your weaknesses are.
No, because I, I, the night therapy doesn't make you any fucking stronger.
I fire the night therapy and he believes that he can diagnose himself.
I do not deny therapy.
You believe that you can diagnose yourself.
Don't you
Super-duper tragic happen like or multiple tragic things happen
The best is shit if you're crying every night
I'm just a realist i'm just being real i'm just being real i'm not making fun of old boy i'm just being real
I don't even know the name of the person but I just know somebody said it
It was either
Was that was a rope was a rope
It wasn't you Joe Joe Joe was you know, you're Joe
It was me
No, Joe, do you really do you really cry every night or were you just trolling?
Don't you dumbass I just mean funny but something I cried once every like seven days
What kind of shit is making you cry every week then
Be an old man if you make me cry a lot be an old panel you
You said what you said
Leakage makes you cry every night
Like in your case you've got something a little bitch like there's no advice for you like
Every week then there's something something's wrong cry once a week
Yeah, what's the week? What the fuck is wrong with you little bitch?
I'm doing fucking work, man. I never wanted to go.
You gotta guard your feelings and emotions, like for pet, like shit like this.
You can take the shit on the pet or not join the pet, man.
I never tried to make you cry on panel that's friendly advice real shit. Like if you're that sensitive, don't you pay me 25% in that profile
Uh, I mean that's what I'm trying to say. I'm not trying to bully nobody. I'm being dead serious
the
I can't be crying like a little fucking baby.
Like, I was trying to go into the panel.
I'm like, ah, I really ought to tear this fucking ugly maggot
again, then I cry.
That's when I cry with Wolfman joints.
So don't join the panel, then, because then really,
there's a little fucking variable with that panel.
We're going to get the third one over there.
Like a little baby.
Hey, yo, Joe, when you wake up, when you get up in the morning,
give your nearest family member the biggest hug,
whoever you're with, your mom, your daughter, your kids,
your wife, anybody, your auntie, uncle.
I don't want to I don't want you to try it for me. I don't care names. I don't I don't want to go
bitch. Just give your family member a hug. The first one you see. You want to run into up and
appreciate something
Your mom a big hug
Give your mom's the biggest hug you can ever give a give her a kiss on the cheek, too
The last time you go see her every fucking day
I'm a little cry baby Luigi say to my face, but say what's he a face? I'm talking to you on panel
I don't know you don't care about like like I don't care nothing about you
Nobody meant to make you cry. I'm giving you that I'm giving you real advice as a man to another man
If you're crying on panels because people hurt your little feelings
just give somebody a hug you need a hug clearly you need a hug brother stop being a little bit
go to sleep wake up give the first person you see a hug that's it
oh by the way this is not legal advice sir
but prescribed drugs of course yeah just stop joining panels on the internet and go be a man
motherfucker
Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don't cry for me. Don
that
the
Yeah, man fucking what do you what do you want help with what do you what's going on do you need I read I think
Need a reading card reading from page. She said
Like so bad that that that you cry at least once a week and that you think is acceptable for grown man to at least
Cry every day or once a week or whatever you said like just to be like a man like you
We need to cry once a week. That makes sense. A man.
No, I'm just saying it's okay to cry sometimes, but every week there's something going on, but absolutely, absolutely.
So what is it that's going on in your life? Like, like, are you struggling with bills?
Are you a junk? Are you a dopehead? Like, do you smoke crack?
Did you did you lose a loved one recently?
Why don't I'm not cracking? I'm being dead at like, did you lose a loved one?
Well, like, what's going on with you?
He did lose the loved one and that's why I have empathy for him. He loves his dog Raven that he really loved
And so he has a dog that he lost a dog.
All right, I'm just.
Yeah, he was raven.
That sucks, brother.
He really, really was.
Listen, it's a part of life.
It's a part of life.
I say, talk shit.
Family and family passes and we'll join you.
We're going to pass and move on.
You got to accept, like, that's a part of life.
Simple it.
Simple a plane.
And you've got another dog.
And you show that dog unconditional love
in a great fucking life again.
And then you feel that pain again.
Where's Raven?
Continue the process.
I'm nobody cool. I've given Raven a better life than Joe
Thank you. Whoever said that thank you
Yeah, so it's okay, dude. Like we're here for you. I would have loved
I mean like I love you. I would have loved raping more. You're my favorite person. I know you're going through it, but like
You I mean it's time to
Let's move on.
Take the pain and turn into strength.
Time to move on.
Yeah, yeah.
Take the pain and channel it into strength.
Everybody moves on in different fucking ways.
Time to move the fuck on.
Fuck that.
Fuck, fuck that.
But we understand that it was important.
Let him grieve the way he needs to fucking grieve.
It's bad
You forget all about rabies
At least we're so mad at you. We broke it's a real man. I'm like I got you. I got you understand the pain deeply
Away, I'm not like still crying about Raven. No, no, it's okay Raven. You know Raven had a good life, but it was time
About like what like what else makes you upset and like to the point where you're gonna cry
Listen Raven had a good life. It was time
Don't know Raven stop bringing her name up for us left the fucking shit at Raven
Stop it nobody's making nobody knock it off. I'll smack you
What's the what's the what else you got going on in your life, bro, I mean we're here we're listening
Maybe maybe you feel guilty that you weren't the best owner to Raven. Maybe
Oh, love we are wolf man, he might smack you hold on to loud
He gonna do that
Not being realistic right now, you know a lot of times when they when they're wondering what comes with grief is also regrets
But don't cruel don't be cruel to anybody. That's not what we're here. Okay. Don't be
Now I know but I we also tried to ask him how many sounds like like what is it?
No, but maybe talking about it could help you
Today some oil, you know oil spilled in my face. I was doing an oil change. Damn, you know, you know
No, do you do you regret do you have any regrets about anything?
The only two regret
The last two football seasons the Ravens had the best team and we think
Get guaranteed you 2025 mark your fucking dollars Ravens going to the Subo boys
Liz I got $20. There's a lion right now. Let's make the bet right now
No, no, no, no, no, no, if you know if you knew me like my motto is I got $20 says this I got $20 says that
Wow, and God, I don't know you and know your motto, you know
That's that's tpp information only exclusive
I mean, I mean, how do we make this pool? I'll throw 20 bucks in the pool
$20 he said $20 that the Ravens make it to the Superbowl. I got $20 says they don't
No
The Ravens make it
I mean, we got Henry Jackson. We got fucking Deandre Hopkins on the team now. We got the defense
Raven's going to feed it this year, I'll say we don't undefeated boy
Ravens losing the first or second round of playoffs
Probably the first round there. Yeah, probably fair enough Ravens lose
Everybody got their team. I just wrote my team wins everybody has their team. I don't got a team
I don't even watch football, but I still take that back Ravens won't make it to the Superbowl
I don't even know if the Ravens are better or bad
Why do you want me to take the bet? I know right? I'm doing the same shit because I don't even know who the Ravens quarterback is
So is it still Lamar Jackson?
You don't even know who the Ravens quarterback is. Wow you a gay. I have I don't know now one single name of any
football player ever
Ravens quarterback is the March
Yo shout out the damn arena right back in the day he was on the dolphins, right?
They want to know who he is. I know who that Tom Bradley Brady Tom Brady do it is home, Brad
The Patriots he was the Patriots. Yeah, like that's all I really know. I don't really fuck with sports
Jojo, oh
I got your money. I'll take your flying now burn
You're gonna spend as you don't a nearest crack dealer
Whatever many quarters is $20, but you're gonna get like 50 quarters
Can it can that be the we whoever wins like that's a thing we put in this the video to fucking back chat of them
Just burning the
When I'm taking that's what I'm spending it. I'm not burning
No, I'm not swishers black I don't smoke like
Oh, I smoke black and mouths very super duper occasionally though. I ain't gonna lie like
Six months, I'll smoke the black if I if I'm drinking it some awesome black
Yeah, oh yeah, yeah the wine is official the wine is official. Yes, sir. That's the flavor, baby
Well, if I do smoke the black amount, it's a wine or or it's a arm. Oh
Mr. Orange rapper jazz jazz jazz
It's sort of like a mob, but say it was caught a black and
Where the fuck is my brother Oliver to Bernie, he's like a fucking brother to me
the
Don't you dare take it to speeda speeda hit the link baby. It's a fucking link
You know that beta is back there. Come on beta
Mustard copy in the chat like in caps like mustard God or what?
moustache got
Isn't Joe shit, please?
My five minutes typed in the chat right quick. Yeah, I think Joe and beat our day
I don't do it don't beat is a girl
He does never
And I always that beat is back
He's a fucking traitor not taking an American. I'm saying is that your girl is that your girl?
your day
Yeah, you're not saying nothing like dude you you saying I'm not saying nothing. It is worse than saying yes or no like
Well, you don't know about it, but it was fucking
That road don't matter eat some fuck
Honestly, yeah, we're on the internet
What the fuck am I doing about it?
Nothing, nothing, nothing
I just prove you're some emotional fucking weirdo
that just can't answer questions
Why am I emotional because I cropped every day?
Yeah
I said it's beating your girl you said, uh, I'm not gonna answer that
What the fuck so that kind of means like yeah, that's my
Like that's so it is
Like yo beat is my bitch
Why do you cry every day?
No, no, no, once a week once he changed it to he changed it was it used to be every day now
It's mostly we change it. He changed it back to every day now. He did
Oh, I heard I was rambling. I hear it. Okay. Okay. Oh my God every 60 minutes. Jesus Christ
What about don't cry? Oh, you're such a real man. You don't ever cry
Joe, but what do you what makes you cry though every day like what is it that's making you cry?
Yeah, I'm like, this ain't got I'm not getting in this with you. You're not
We wouldn't try to help you
We're all we're all just like you okay, we're all the same so what what is it this making you cry?
That was funny whoever said that we're trying to help you
Thank you guys. Yeah, you're trying to help him out. You're well. Yeah, we're helping you right now
So what is it?
Was making a friend little baby
No, I mean Joe like not telling us is gonna get you cracked on way more
But if you told us and we took you serious, it's like oh shit. All right guys
They ain't gonna play about really going really going through some shit like and then we would fall back
You know
It's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it
basically that's yeah did your wife bang the pool boy keep it real or did she
bang or did the pool boy bang you
maybe they were both fucking the pool boy he's both fucking the pool boy my
faves
got him bitch
there was both banging the pool boy got him
Got the fuck out of the way you throw my pool boys, man
Banging a pool boy, I got your bitch
On a serious note though really what's got you bothered by no, how long have you been crying like that man? I'm actually worried about you
Ever since his wife banged the pool boy first is that what it was
100% 100%
I'm worried about site. We're a site cat. I'm worried about him. Don't worry about
Like he's okay. He's okay. We're worried about you right now
Shout out to psyche in this channel
Oh shit got the backwards head on gangsta you are
No
Why is that shit so brown that's supposed to be a clear bong though you turned it
It's fucking guy bro. He smoked way too much hash out of that but makes it with some own some some some some crack
He got black
Yo Joe, change your hat to the backwards when you're taking a hit.
Change your hat backwards.
No, that's his cap.
No, that way we know you're serious.
He got track marks, my pain.
He's not playing with me.
Yo, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Yo Joe don't do that shit no more you are
Yo keep keep the hat on or off what are you doing family put it on take it off
You know anybody
Put your head on, put your f...
Put that fucking head on you ginger
You're spitting a spitting image
Put the fucking head on ginger
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Grow a beard, you look like fucking Santa Claus
You are...
No, no bro
Hey Joe, do me a favor
Do me a favor, do me a favor
You look like a strong fucking Caucasian brother
Stop
Crying yeah, we don't do that stop
Whenever you feel a crack
Put your feelings just stuff those feelings like deep in
I'll see your tits. I'd say yeah
Matter of fact, you came up going to the garage and show us your BMX bike
We all know you got a BMX bike or a skateboard show us one of them right now
I want to see the BMX or the on the skateboard right now. He's either a skateboarder or a BMX do
2011 for Bronco
I don't do I don't drive to the liquor store, but I'm drinking
What are you drinking a bottle of lotion what was that a bottle of a bottle of lotion what the fuck was that?
Say there
He showed a bottle of fucking lotion.
Or after you started the beer, you drink a bottle of lotion.
Tell me that Joe was dating clarity.
It looked like a plastic bottle of lotion.
What the fuck?
They broke up.
He's never been the same.
Says the guys that won't turn the camera on.
You guys that won't dare turn the camera on.
Shut up, Luigi.
You're speaking of we see one of the sides I've ever seen on slight span on be honest
No offense. You're one of the gayest guys. I've ever fucking seen up your book. It wasn't it you the bottom of
No, that was easy never
Say I don't you want to I don't chew on the phone
No, what are you one of these fuckers bottom of thought?
It's better to be cool with me than to like be against me
Hey, you still
You could come back on my side, we'll be good you are I promise
Racist what are you talking about racist nobody said none of our race
Look
Raven would have wanted somebody says something about stuffy diamonds. What's a scuffy diamond? That's a that's a that's a person
No, no, listen
Joe Raven never wanted this for you, man. You never wanted this
Oh, you're saying it's a man does a man that named himself flirty diamonds. It's a tranny name
What's training me training training is this a man training is listening if my engine goes in my car
I'm fucked if my tranny goes in my car. I'm fucked
I'm training, training is a man, he's a floaty devil, he's an excellent woman, a man on hormones, yes.
Oh
Don't tell me you're out here fucking transmissions, bro. I mean
You look
I like it. I love it. I want some fucking more of it. I try
You like
What are you drinking man, what are you drinking to forget? I'm talking one natural like
No wonder he cries once a week
Yo, if I'm if a grown man that thinks he's a heterosexual is fucking a trainee
You're fucking a man named scruffy diamonds, bro
That thinks he's a woman
And her name is a flirt for a scuffy flirty whatever the fucking diamonds
Name is I'll say it
Man, I never wanted this for you Raven never wanted this for you
stay dirty and want this for you neither
nobody wanted this
I don't even know
nobody wanted this for you
cries
but he's in love
did you love him
he's in love with a trident
no really really did you
did you love him though
yeah he did love
Are you talking to me that I love who?
Do you like the train's end you like the transmission the
Where you would love the fucking train where you were left with a man
Was you in love with a man yes or no, yes or no
That's my answer. I do consider first time in a party
But you could have been in love with a man
So I want that that's what oh, I'm not
Now, okay. Okay. Now I understand why you cry every day or every week or every with
I understand why you cry very often now. I get it. I get it
Make sure you stated don't bring that shit back to our women even
Maybe they would have a good reason to cry.
That attitude, man.
What attitude?
What?
He doesn't like my attitude.
He's talking to Isaiah.
Does our friends would have fucking
You fucked another man you fucked another man
Oh god
You smoked
Ayo thing thing ayo thing. I got got him got him. I got him bitch. I got this bitch
Who are you?